So one shortcut. Maybe you notice that the formula for the weight can also be written as
有一个简单算法 大家可能注意到
the natural logarithm of the number of
权重公式也可以写成
correctly classified points divided by the number of incorrectly classified points.
正确分类的点的数量除以错误分类的点的数量所得商的自然对数
This is just obtained by multiplying the top and bottom of the formula
要得到这个公式
inside the logarithm by the number of data points.
只需要将自然对数内分子 分母分别乘以点的数量即可
So in the first model we have seven points correctly classified and one incorrect,
所以第一个模型中 我们有 7 个正确分类的点和 1 个错误分类的点
therefore the weight is the natural logarithm of seven divided by one which is 1.95.
因此 权重即是 7 除以 1 所得商的自然对数 即 1.95
Equivalently, the second one has weight logarithm of four
同样 第二个模型的权重是 4 除以 4 所得商的自然对数
divided by four which is logarithm of one which is zero.
即 1 的自然对数 是 0
This makes sense as the model has 50% accuracy, so it's useless.
这个结果正确 因为准确率是 50% 所以这个模型没有用
And for the third one we have two correct ones and six incorrect ones,
第三个模型中 有 2 个正确分类的点和 6 个错误分类的点
so the weight of this is logarithm of two divided by six,
所以这个模型的权重是 2 除以 6 所得商的自然对数
which is minus 1.099.
即负的 1.099
Notice that the weight is negative,
注意这个权重值是负数
which means we listen to this model but we will do
这意味着我们不舍弃这个模型
the exact opposite as it says since it lies most of the time.
但我们采纳与其相反的决策 因为这个模型大多数时候都是错误的
Now what about these two models?
那这两个模型呢？
The first one has weight logarithm of eight over
第一个模型的权重是 8 除以 0 所得商的自然对数
zero since it makes no mistakes. What is it?
因为这个模型不犯错 但这是什么意思？
And even worse the second one has logarithm of zero over
更糟糕的是 第二个模型的权重是 0 除以 8 所得商的自然对数
eight which is logarithm of zero which is undefined too. What do we do?
也就是 0 的自然对数 根本不存在 那要怎么做？
Well, we can think of eight over zero as infinity,
我们可以设想 8 除以 0 的结果是无穷大
so the first one has weight infinity and for
所以第一个模型的权重是正无穷
the second one we can think of the logarithm of zero as negative infinity.
第二个模型  我们可以认为 0 的自然对数是负无穷
So the second one has weight negative infinity.
所以第二个模型的权重是负无穷
Now, does this make sense? Well, let's think about it.
这有道理吗？我们来想一下
This would mess up our calculations
这打乱了我们的计算方式
but if one of our weak learners classifies the data perfectly,
但如果我们的弱学习器中 有一个非常棒地完成了分类任务
then we're pretty much done, right?
那几乎就大功告成了 对吧？
This says, listen to it infinitely and
也就是说 无穷大的相信这个模型的建议
don't listen to the others and the second one same thing.
不听其他模型的建议 第二个模型也是一样
If one of our weak learners manages to get everything wrong,
如果有一个弱学习器在分类时候把所有点都分错了
then doing the complete opposite already classifies our data well.
那么采纳与它相反的决策几乎就正确地完成了分类任务了
So assigning it a weight of minus infinity just says,
所以给它赋予一个负无穷的权重就意味着
just listen to this model but do
听这个模型的建议
the complete opposite and don't worry about the other models.
但采纳与它相反的决策 不要管其他的模型
These two are not very likely to happen in the practice,
事实上 这两种模型不太可能发生
so this is actually not very concerning.
所以没什么可担心的
It's still good to know what happens in
但为了一致性检查 仍然有必要
extreme cases for consistency checks like this one.
来分析这样的极端案例